[
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為a?",
    "choice1": "お",
    "choice2": "こ",
    "choice3": "あ",
    "choice4": "え",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為i?",
    "choice1": "い",
    "choice2": "く",
    "choice3": "う",
    "choice4": "お",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為u?",
    "choice1": "く",
    "choice2": "あ",
    "choice3": "け",
    "choice4": "う",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為e?",
    "choice1": "う",
    "choice2": "か",
    "choice3": "え",
    "choice4": "け",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為o?",
    "choice1": "く",
    "choice2": "お",
    "choice3": "あ",
    "choice4": "う",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為ka?",
    "choice1": "あ",
    "choice2": "か",
    "choice3": "こ",
    "choice4": "う",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為ki?",
    "choice1": "き",
    "choice2": "か",
    "choice3": "あ",
    "choice4": "け",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為ku?",
    "choice1": "け",
    "choice2": "う",
    "choice3": "お",
    "choice4": "く",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為ke?",
    "choice1": "き",
    "choice2": "い",
    "choice3": "あ",
    "choice4": "け",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "下列何者發音為ko?",
    "choice1": "あ",
    "choice2": "か",
    "choice3": "こ",
    "choice4": "う",
    "answer": 3
  }
]